Guide to the Nadine P. Winter Council of the District of Columbia papers, Circa 1976-1990 MS2188
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
- Environmental issues, 1984-1990; Series 5
  - Litter and Solid Waste Reduction Donation Letter, 1987; Series 5 (Box 99, Folder 6)
  - Litter and Solid Waste Reduction - Fact Sheet, Undated; Series 5 (Box 99, Folder 7)
  - Litter and Solid Waste Reduction - Media, 1987; Series 5 (Box 99, Folder 8)
  - Local Emergency Planning Committee - Meetings, 1987-1988; Series 5 (Box 99, Folder 9)
  - Local Emergency Planning Committee - Membership, 1986; Series 5 (Box 99, Folder 10)
  - Lorton Landfill Tour, 1990; Series 5 (Box 99, Folder 11)
  - Marion Barry - Hazardous Materials and Emergency Planning, 1988; Series 5 (Box 99, Folder 12)
  - Maryland Association of Soil Conservation Districts, 1990; Series 5 (Box 99, Folder 13)
  - Materials on Recycling [1/2], Undated; Series 5 (Box 99, Folder 14)
  - Materials on Recycling [2/2], Undated; Series 5 (Box 99, Folder 15)
  - Materials on Recycling [1/2], Undated; Series 5 (Box 100, Folder 1)
  - Materials on Recycling [2/2], Undated; Series 5 (Box 100, Folder 2)
  - Materials on Recycling [1/2], Undated; Series 5 (Box 100, Folder 3)
  - Materials on Recycling [2/2], Undated; Series 5 (Box 100, Folder 4)
  - Newsletters, Brochures [1/2], 1988; Series 5 (Box 100, Folder 5)
  - Newsletters, Brochures [2/2], 1988; Series 5 (Box 101, Folder 1)
  - NYC Department of Sanitation Curbside Recycling Program, Undated; Series 5 (Box 101, Folder 2)
  - New York City Recycling, Undated; Series 5 (Box 101, Folder 3)
  - Ocean County Recycling, 1988; Series 5 (Box 101, Folder 4)
  - Office of Emergency Preparedness, 1984-1988; Series 5 (Box 101, Folder 5)
  - Office for Environmental Growth, 1987; Series 5 (Box 101, Folder 6)
  - Office of Recycling, 1990; Series 5 (Box 101, Folder 7)
  - Operation Igloo, 1987; Series 5 (Box 101, Folder 8)
  - Organization for Environmental Growth, Undated; Series 5 (Box 101, Folder 9)
  - Pesticides, Undated; Series 5 (Box 101, Folder 10)
  - Plastics and Styrofoams, 1988-1989; Series 5 (Box 101, Folder 11)
  - Potomac River, 1988; Series 5 (Box 101, Folder 12)
  - Proposal for DC Recycling Centers, Undated; Series 5 (Box 101, Folder 13)
  - Radio Advertising, 1988; Series 5 (Box 102, Folder 1)
  - Radon, 1988; Series 5 (Box 102, Folder 2)
  - Recycling, Undated; Series 5 (Box 102, Folder 3)
  - Recycling, 1988; Series 5 (Box 102, Folder 4)
  - Recycling, 1990; Series 5 (Box 102, Folder 5)
  - Recycling [1/3], 1987-1988; Series 5 (Box 102, Folder 6)
  - Recycling [2/3], 1988; Series 5 (Box 102, Folder 7)
  - Recycling [3/3], 1988; Series 5 (Box 103, Folder 1)
  - Recycling - Advertisements, Undated; Series 5 (Box 103, Folder 2)
  - Recycling Articles [1/2], 1988-1989; Series 5 (Box 103, Folder 3)
  - Recycling Articles [2/2], 1988-1989; Series 5 (Box 103, Folder 4)
  - Recycling Centers, 1989; Series 5 (Box 103, Folder 5)
  - Recycling - Europe [1/2], 1988; Series 5 (Box 103, Folder 6)
  - Recycling - Europe [2/2], 1988; Series 5 (Box 104, Folder 1)
  - Recycling Forum, 1989; Series 5 (Box 104, Folder 2)
  - Recycling - General Information, 1989; Series 5 (Box 104, Folder 3)
  - Recycling Legislation, 1987; Series 5 (Box 104, Folder 4)
  - Recycling Legislation, 1988; Series 5 (Box 104, Folder 5)
  - Recycling - Other Jurisdictions [1/2], Undated; Series 5 (Box 104, Folder 6)
  - Recycling Program, 1989-1990; Series 5 (Box 104, Folder 7)
  - Recycling - Other Jurisdictions [2/2], Undated; Series 5 (Box 105, Folder 2)
  - Recycling - Testimony [1/5], 1987-1988; Series 5 (Box 105, Folder 3)
  - Recycling - Testimony [2/5], 1987-1988; Series 5 (Box 105, Folder 4)
  - Recycling - Testimony [3/5], 1987-1988; Series 5 (Box 105, Folder 5)
  - Recycling Testimony [4/5], 1987-1988; Series 5 (Box 106, Folder 1)
  - Recycling - Testimony [5/5], 1987-1988; Series 5 (Box 106, Folder 2)
  - Recycling Working Grove, Undated; Series 5 (Box 106, Folder 3)
  - Recycling Tours, 1990; Series 5 (Box 106, Folder 4)
  - Resource Recovery Program, 1987; Series 5 (Box 106, Folder 5)
  - Rutgers - Recycling, 1988; Series 5 (Box 106, Folder 6)
  - Scher, Barry, Undated; Series 5 (Box 106, Folder 7)
  - St. Vincent DePaul Society, 1989; Series 5 (Box 106, Folder 8)
  - Sewer Overflow, Undated; Series 5 (Box 106, Folder 9)
  - Sludge Disposal, 1986; Series 5 (Box 106, Folder 10)
  - Soil Erosion, 1986; Series 5 (Box 106, Folder 11)
  - Source Separation and Recycling, 1981; Series 5 (Box 106, Folder 12)
  - Spring Clean-up Week, 1988; Series 5 (Box 106, Folder 13)
  - Standard Directory of Advertisers 1986, Series 5 (Box 106, Folder 14)
  - Ticonderoga Farms - Recycling, 1988; Series 5 (Box 106, Folder 15)
  - Solid Waste, 1986; Series 5 (Box 107, Folder 1)
  - Solid Waste [1/2], 1988-1989; Series 5 (Box 107, Folder 2)
  - Solid Waste, 1988-1989; Series 5 (Box 107, Folder 3)
  - Training Program Blue Plains, 1988; Series 5 (Box 107, Folder 4)
  - Tree Planting and Beautification, 1990; Series 5 (Box 107, Folder 5)
  - VA Department of Conservation and Economic Development, 1984; Series 5 (Box 107, Folder 6)
  - Water, 1988; Series 5 (Box 107, Folder 7)
  - Water and Sewer News, 1988; Series 5 (Box 107, Folder 8)
  - Water Resources Planning Board, 1986-1988; Series 5 (Box 107, Folder 9)
  - The Way We Diaper, 1990; Series 5 (Box 107, Folder 10)
- Community development/Ward Six, 1982-1990; Series 6
  This series contains correspondence, reports, and other documents related to various community topics including H Street Community Development Corporation; Southeast Neighborhood Development Corporation, Anacostia beautification, Advisory Neighborhood commissions, eastern market revitalization, and community meetings.
  - 1A Advisory Neighborhood Commission, 1989-1990; Series 6 (Box 108, Folder 1)
  - 1B Advisory Neighborhood Commission, 1989-1990; Series 6 (Box 108, Folder 2)
  - 1C Advisory Neighborhood Commission, 1988-1989; Series 6 (Box 108, Folder 3)
  - ANC 1 D, 1989; Series 6 (Box 108, Folder 4)
  - 1E Advisory Neighborhood Commission, 1986-1989; Series 6 (Box 108, Folder 5)
  - 2A Advisory Neighborhood Commission, 1988; Series 6 (Box 108, Folder 6)
  - 2B Advisory Neighborhood Commission, 1989-1990; Series 6 (Box 108, Folder 7)
  - 2C Advisory Neighborhood Commission, 1990; Series 6 (Box 108, Folder 8)
  - 2D Advisory Neighborhood Commission, 1990; Series 6 (Box 108, Folder 9)
  - 3C Advisory Neighborhood Commission, 1986-1989; Series 6 (Box 108, Folder 10)
  - Advisory Neighborhood Commission 3-D, Undated; Series 6 (Box 108, Folder 11)
  - 3E Advisory Neighborhood Commission, 1986-1989; Series 6 (Box 108, Folder 12)
  - 3F Advisory Neighborhood Commission, 1986-1989; Series 6 (Box 108, Folder 13)
  - 3G Advisory Neighborhood Commission, 1986-1989; Series 6 (Box 108, Folder 14)
  - 4A Advisory Neighborhood Association, 1987; Series 6 (Box 108, Folder 15)
  - 4C Advisory Neighborhood Commission, 1986-1990; Series 6 (Box 108, Folder 16)
  - 4D Advisory Neighborhood Commission, 1985-1988; Series 6 (Box 108, Folder 17)
  - 6A Advisory Neighborhood Commission, 1989-1990; Series 6 (Box 108, Folder 18)
  - 6A ANC - Walk Through, 1988; Series 6 (Box 108, Folder 19)
  - 6B Advisory Neighborhood Commission, 1990; Series 6 (Box 108, Folder 20)
  - 6C Advisory Neighborhood Commission, 1986-1990; Series 6 (Box 108, Folder 21)
  - Advisory Neighborhood Commission 7B, 1986; Series 6 (Box 108, Folder 22)
  - 7D Advisory Neighborhood Commission, 1988-1989; Series 6 (Box 108, Folder 23)
  - 7th and I Neighborhood Watch, 1989; Series 6 (Box 108, Folder 24)
  - 800 N Capitol St. Project, 1990; Series 6 (Box 108, Folder 25)
  - 1300 Maryland Ave Parking, 1984; Series 6 (Box 108, Folder 26)
  - 1700 Block of Gales St., 1985; Series 6 (Box 108, Folder 27)
  - 2100 MLK Ave Groudbreaking, 1988; Series 6 (Box 108, Folder 28)
  - Advisory Neighborhood Commission Lists, 1987-1989; Series 6 (Box 109, Folder 1)
  - Advisory Neighborhood Commisioner, 1988; Series 6 (Box 109, Folder 2)
  - Alley Cleaning, 1989; Series 6 (Box 109, Folder 3)
  - Anacostia Beautification and Gateway Project, 1987; Series 6 (Box 109, Folder 4)
  - Anacostia Gateway and Beautification Project, Undated; Series 6 (Box 109, Folder 5)
  - Anacostia Network, 1987; Series 6 (Box 109, Folder 6)
  - Anacostia Coordination Council, 1990; Series 6 (Box 109, Folder 7)
  - Anacostia D.P.W. Environmental Health, Health Technicians C/O Frankie Cox, 1987; Series 6 (Box 109, Folder 8)
  - Anacostia Development, 1984-1988; Series 6 (Box 109, Folder 9)
  - Anacostia Development, 1989; Series 6 (Box 109, Folder 10)
  - Anacostia Economic Development Corporation, 1989-1990; Series 6 (Box 109, Folder 11)
  - Arboretum Neighborhood Association, 1986; Series 6 (Box 109, Folder 12)
  - Anacostia Office Building Grand Opening, 1990; Series 6 (Box 109, Folder 13)
  - Atlas Theatre 1987 DC Inaugral Committee, Series 6 (Box 109, Folder 14)
  - Atlas Theatre Gov't. of DC Dept. Human Services, 1987; Series 6 (Box 109, Folder 15)
  - H Street CDC Bill Barrow, 1987; Series 6 (Box 109, Folder 16)
  - Atlas Theatre Bernes Asset Management, 1988; Series 6 (Box 109, Folder 17)
  - Atlas Theatre Budget Amendment Contract, 1988; Series 6 (Box 109, Folder 18)
  - Atlas Theatre David Burka, 1987; Series 6 (Box 109, Folder 19)
  - Atlas Theatre DC Public School Letter, 1986; Series 6 (Box 109, Folder 20)
  - Atlas Theatre Duke Ellington School of the Arts, 1986; Series 6 (Box 109, Folder 21)
  - Atlas Theatre for H Street CDC, 1987; Series 6 (Box 109, Folder 22)
  - Atlas Theatre 1987 H Street CDC, Undated; Series 6 (Box 109, Folder 23)
  - Atkas Theatre Income Projections, Undated; Series 6 (Box 109, Folder 24)
  - Atlas Theatre Kan Kouran, 1987; Series 6 (Box 109, Folder 25)
  - Atlas Theatre Meeting, 1988; Series 6 (Box 109, Folder 26)
  - Atlas Theatre Members Addresses, Undated; Series 6 (Box 109, Folder 27)
  - Atlas Theatre News Articles, Undated; Series 6 (Box 109, Folder 28)
  - Atlas Theatre Pro Forma Medical, 1987; Series 6 (Box 109, Folder 29)
  - Atlas Theatre properties Rate Schedule, 1987; Series 6 (Box 109, Folder 30)
  - Atlas Theatre Proposal to Create an Art Center, 1987; Series 6 (Box 109, Folder 31)
  - Atlas Theatre Wylie Street Town Houses, Undated; Series 6 (Box 109, Folder 32)
  - Block Clubs, Undated; Series 6 (Box 110, Folder 1)
  - Capital East Apartments, 1985; Series 6 (Box 110, Folder 2)
  - Capitol Hill East Coalition, 1990; Series 6 (Box 110, Folder 3)
  - Capitol Hill Restoration Society, 1989-1990; Series 6 (Box 110, Folder 4)
  - Capitol Hill Traffic Task Force, 1990; Series 6 (Box 110, Folder 5)
  - Cordozo-Shaw Neighborhood Association, 1990; Series 6 (Box 110, Folder 6)
  - Christmas in Anacostia, 1990; Series 6 (Box 110, Folder 7)
  - Christmas Party, 1983; Series 6 (Box 110, Folder 8)
  - Clean Up, 1990; Series 6 (Box 110, Folder 9)
  - Community Meeting - Crime, 1990; Series 6 (Box 110, Folder 10)
  - Community Meeting about Neighborhood Crime Prevention, 1990; Series 6 (Box 110, Folder 11)
  - Robert Crosby Carriage House, 1986; Series 6 (Box 110, Folder 12)
  - D.C. Eastern Market Planning Committee, 1986; Series 6 (Box 110, Folder 13)
  - Downtown Development District, 1990; Series 6 (Box 110, Folder 14)
  - Fredrick Douglass Community Important Council, 1985; Series 6 (Box 110, Folder 15)
  - Eastern Market, Undated; Series 6 (Box 110, Folder 16)
  - Eastern Market, 1988; Series 6 (Box 110, Folder 17)
  - Eastern Market, 1987; Series 6 (Box 110, Folder 18)
  - Eastern Market, 1987; Series 6 (Box 110, Folder 19)
  - Eastern Market, 1987; Series 6 (Box 110, Folder 20)
  - Eastern Market, 1986; Series 6 (Box 110, Folder 21)
  - Eastern Market, 1990; Series 6 (Box 110, Folder 22)
  - Eastern Market Community Development Corporation [1/2], 1988; Series 6 (Box 111, Folder 1)
  - Eastern Market Community Development Corporation [2/2], 1988; Series 6 (Box 111, Folder 2)
  - Eastern Market neighborhood Commission, 1986-1987; Series 6 (Box 111, Folder 3)
  - Eastern Market Neighborhood Commission Mailing List, Undated; Series 6 (Box 111, Folder 4)
  - Eastern Market Preservation and Development Corporation, 1990; Series 6 (Box 111, Folder 5)
  - Ellen Wilson Public Housing, 1989; Series 6 (Box 111, Folder 6)
  - Ellen Wilson Study, Undated; Series 6 (Box 111, Folder 7)
  - Gateway, 1989; Series 6 (Box 111, Folder 8)
  - Gateways to Washington, 1987; Series 6 (Box 111, Folder 9)
  - H St. Businessmen, 1989; Series 6 (Box 111, Folder 10)
  - H St. Community Development, 1986-1989; Series 6 (Box 111, Folder 11)
  - H St. Community Development Corporation, 1989; Series 6 (Box 112, Folder 1)
  - H St CDC [1/2], 1986; Series 6 (Box 112, Folder 2)
  - H St CDC [2/2], 1986; Series 6 (Box 112, Folder 3)
  - H St CDC, 1986; Series 6 (Box 112, Folder 4)
  - H St CDC, 1986; Series 6 (Box 112, Folder 5)
  - H St CDC, Undated; Series 6 (Box 112, Folder 6)
  - H St CDC Board Directs Meeting - Minutes, 1988; Series 6 (Box 112, Folder 7)
  - H St CDC Development Corp.'s Bylaws, 1989; Series 6 (Box 112, Folder 8)
  - H St CDC Desum - 89. XLS, 1988; Series 6 (Box 112, Folder 9)
  - H St CDC Committee on Education & Libraries, 1990; Series 6 (Box 112, Folder 10)
  - Executive Directors H St CDC, 1989; Series 6 (Box 112, Folder 11)
  - H St CDC Facade Loan Status Report, 1988; Series 6 (Box 112, Folder 12)
  - H St CDC Fiscal Year 1988 Summary, Undated; Series 6 (Box 112, Folder 13)
  - H St CDC Fund Raising, 1987; Series 6 (Box 112, Folder 14)
  - H St CDC - James Tatum, 1990; Series 6 (Box 112, Folder 15)
  - H St CDC - Management Report, 1987; Series 6 (Box 112, Folder 16)
  - H St CDC Management Service Agreement, 1986; Series 6 (Box 112, Folder 17)
  - H St CDC - Mailing List, Undated; Series 6 (Box 112, Folder 18)
  - H St CDC Memos, 1988; Series 6 (Box 112, Folder 19)
  - H St CDC National Urban Coalition, 1988; Series 6 (Box 113, Folder 1)
  - H St CDC Neighborhood Commercial Revil., 1989; Series 6 (Box 113, Folder 2)
  - H St CDC - Neighborhood Commercial Revitalization Program, 1988; Series 6 (Box 113, Folder 3)
  - H St CDC - OBED, 1987; Series 6 (Box 113, Folder 4)
  - H St CDC Parcel #7, 1989; Series 6 (Box 113, Folder 5)
  - H St CDC Progress & Status Report/BLP, Undated; Series 6 (Box 113, Folder 6)
  - H St CDC Projected Development Cost, 1986; Series 6 (Box 113, Folder 7)
  - H St Property Listings, Undated; Series 6 (Box 113, Folder 8)
  - H St CDC - Proposal, 1985; Series 6 (Box 113, Folder 9)
  - H St CDC Development of RLA Parcel #22, 1989; Series 6 (Box 113, Folder 10)
  - H St Revitalization Attendees, Undated; Series 6 (Box 113, Folder 11)
  - H St CDC - Transportation Committee, 1987; Series 6 (Box 113, Folder 12)
  - H St CDC Statement of Revenue and Expenditures, 1988; Series 6 (Box 113, Folder 13)
  - H St CDC Arthur Williams, 1987; Series 6 (Box 113, Folder 14)
  - H St Corridor Building Corporation, 1988; Series 6 (Box 113, Folder 15)
  - H St Merchants Association, 1990; Series 6 (Box 113, Folder 16)
  - H St Mural, 1986; Series 6 (Box 113, Folder 17)
  - H St Revitalization, 1984-1986; Series 6 (Box 113, Folder 18)
  - H St Connection Shopping Center, 1990; Series 6 (Box 113, Folder 19)
  - H St Shopping Center Ground Breaking, Undated; Series 6 (Box 113, Folder 20)
  - H St Tape Recording, 1987; Series 6 (Box 113, Folder 21)
  - H St Vacant Properties, Undated; Series 6 (Box 113, Folder 22)
  - Kingman Park, 1990; Series 6 (Box 114, Folder 1)
  - Lamand Community, 1988; Series 6 (Box 114, Folder 2)
  - Linden Neighborhood Association, 1989; Series 6 (Box 114, Folder 3)
  - Market Row Association, 1990; Series 6 (Box 114, Folder 4)
  - Marshall Heights CDC - Homeshare, 1989; Series 6 (Box 114, Folder 5)
  - Martin Luther King Jr. Ave SE, 1986; Series 6 (Box 114, Folder 6)
  - Martin Luther King Ave & V St SE Development, 1986; Series 6 (Box 114, Folder 7)
  - McMillian Park Committee, 1989; Series 6 (Box 114, Folder 8)
  - Near Northeast Community Improvement Corporation, 1988; Series 6 (Box 114, Folder 9)
  - Neighborhood Development, 1989; Series 6 (Box 114, Folder 10)
  - Neighborhood Housing Services, 1990; Series 6 (Box 114, Folder 11)
  - neighborhood Legal Services, 1986; Series 6 (Box 114, Folder 12)
  - Neighborhood Traffic Management, 1986; Series 6 (Box 114, Folder 3)
  - Neighborhood Walk, 1990; Series 6 (Box 114, Folder 14)
  - North Carolina 115th St SE, 1985; Series 6 (Box 114, Folder 15)
  - Oklahoma Ave Block Club, 1986; Series 6 (Box 114, Folder 16)
  - Oklahoma Avenue NE Athletic Field, 1986; Series 6 (Box 114, Folder 17)
  - Ordway Gardens Condominium, 1987; Series 6 (Box 114, Folder 18)
  - Parcel 18 Limited Partnership, 1987; Series 6 (Box 114, Folder 19)
  - Parcel 22, Undated; Series 6 (Box 114, Folder 20)
  - Potomac Development Corporation, 1988; Series 6 (Box 114, Folder 21)
  - Reed-Cooke Neighborhood Association, 1988; Series 6 (Box 114, Folder 22)
  - Residents Council, 1987; Series 6 (Box 114, Folder 23)
  - Revitalization of Martin Luther King Avenue & Good Hope Road SE Business Area of Ward Six, 1986; Series 6 (Box 114, Folder 24)
  - Shaw Coalition Redevelopment Corporation, 1986; Series 6 (Box 114, Folder 25)
  - Shaw PAC, 1986; Series 6 (Box 114, Folder 26)
  - Silver Market Coalition, 1990; Series 6 (Box 114, Folder 27)
  - Silver Market Neighborhood Coalition, 1990; Series 6 (Box 114, Folder 28)
  - Sousa Neighborhood Association, 1990; Series 6 (Box 114, Folder 29)
  - South Carolina Block Club, Undated; Series 6 (Box 114, Folder 30)
  - Southeast Area Community Development Corporation, Undated; Series 6 (Box 114, Folder 31)
  - Southeast House [1/2], 1990; Series 6 (Box 114, Folder 32)
  - Southeast House [2/2], 1990; Series 6 (Box 115, Folder 1)
  - SNDC - 2100 Martin Luther King, 1989; Series 6 (Box 115, Folder 2)
  - SE Neighborhood Development Commission, 1987; Series 6 (Box 115, Folder 3)
  - SE Neighborhood Development Commission, 1987; Series 6 (Box 115, Folder 4)
  - SE Neighborhood Development Corporation, 1988; Series 6 (Box 115, Folder 5)
  - Southeast Neighborhood Development Corporation, 1990; Series 6 (Box 115, Folder 6)
  - SNDC, 1987; Series 6 (Box 115, Folder 7)
  - SE Neighborhood Development Corporation - Appointments, 1987; Series 6 (Box 115, Folder 8)
  - SE Neighborhood Development Corporation - Articles of Incorporation, 1987; Series 6 (Box 115, Folder 9)
  - SNDC - Articles of Incorporation, 1987; Series 6 (Box 115, Folder 10)
  - SNDC - Board of Directors, 1988; Series 6 (Box 115, Folder 11)
  - SNDC - Bylaws, Undated; Series 6 (Box 115, Folder 12)
  - SNDC - Jones, Lawrence, Undated; Series 6 (Box 115, Folder 13)
  - SNDC - Local Initiation Support, 1987; Series 6 (Box 115, Folder 14)
  - SNDC - Mailing List, Undated; Series 6 (Box 115, Folder 15)
  - SNDC - Mayoral Appointees, Undated; Series 6 (Box 115, Folder 16)
  - SNDC - Meetings, 1987; Series 6 (Box 115, Folder 17)
  - SNDC - Minutes of Meeting, 1987; Series 6 (Box 115, Folder 18)
  - Southeast Neighborhood Development Corporation - David Nesbitt, 1987; Series 6 (Box 115, Folder 19)
  - Southeast Neighborhood Development Corporation - Mayoral Nominees, 1989; Series 6 (Box 115, Folder 20)
  - SE Neighborhood Development Corporation - Perpetual Savings Bank, 1987; Series 6 (Box 115, Folder 21)
  - SE Neighborhood Development Corporation - Projected Expenditures, 1988-1989; Series 6 (Box 115, Folder 22)
  - SNDC - OBED, 1987; Series 6 (Box 115, Folder 23)
  - SNDC - Organizations, Undated; Series 6 (Box 115, Folder 24)
  - SNDC - Participating Organization Appointees, Undated; Series 6 (Box 116, Folder 1)
  - SNDC - Proposed Work Program, 1987; Series 6 (Box 116, Folder 2)
  - SNDC - Swearing In, 1987; Series 6 (Box 116, Folder 3)
  - Stanton Park Neighborhood Association, 1989; Series 6 (Box 116, Folder 4)
  - Toll Gate Neighborhood Association, 1988-1990; Series 6 (Box 116, Folder 5)
  - Traffic Problems, 1989; Series 6 (Box 116, Folder 6)
  - Tollgate Block Club, Undated; Series 6 (Box 116, Folder 7)
  - Urban Gardens, 1990; Series 6 (Box 116, Folder 8)
  - Upper Cardoza ANC, 1990; Series 6 (Box 116, Folder 9)
  - Upper Cardoza Advisory Neighborhood Commission, 1989; Series 6 (Box 116, Folder 10)
  - Vacant Buildings - Good Hope/MLK St SE, Undated; Series 6 (Box 116, Folder 11)
  - Voting Precincts in Ward Six, Undated; Series 6 (Box 116, Folder 12)
  - Walk-Through, 1990; Series 6 (Box 116, Folder 13)
  - Ward 5 Unity in the Community Day, 1990; Series 6 (Box 116, Folder 14)
  - Ward Plan, 1989; Series 6 (Box 116, Folder 15)
  - Ward Plan Community Advisory Committees for Ward Six, Undated; Series 6 (Box 116, Folder 16)
  - Ward Six, 1990; Series 6 (Box 116, Folder 17)
  - Ward 6 ANC's, 1987; Series 6 (Box 116, Folder 18)
  - Ward Six Beautification, 1990; Series 6 (Box 116, Folder 19)
  - Ward Six Beautification Award Ceremony, 1990; Series 6 (Box 116, Folder 20)
  - Ward Six Clean-Up, 1990; Series 6 (Box 116, Folder 21)
  - Ward Six Community Breakfast, 1989; Series 6 (Box 116, Folder 22)
  - Ward Six Community Leaders, Undated; Series 6 (Box 116, Folder 23)
  - Ward Six Day Festival, 1982; Series 6 (Box 116, Folder 24)
  - Ward Six Democrats, 1989; Series 6 (Box 116, Folder 25)
  - Ward Six Drug Stats, Undated; Series 6 (Box 116, Folder 26)
  - Ward Six Maps, Undated; Series 6 (Box 116, Folder 27)
  - Ward Six Meeting, 1990; Series 6 (Box 116, Folder 28)
  - Ward Six Mini Commission on Aging, Undated; Series 6 (Box 116, Folder 29)
  - Ward Six Neighborhood Partnership Program Committee, 1986; Series 6 (Box 116, Folder 30)
  - Ward Six Picnic, 1989; Series 6 (Box 116, Folder 31)
  - Welcome to Ward Six, 1989; Series 6 (Box 116, Folder 32)
  - Ellen Wilson and Potomac Gardens Public Housing, 1986; Series 6 (Box 116, Folder 33)
  - Wylie Court Settlement, 1986; Series 6 (Box 116, Folder 34)
  - Wylie St. NE, 1986; Series 6 (Box 116, Folder 35)
  - You Name It Anacostia, 1987; Series 6 (Box 116, Folder 36)